Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
7th of March, 1892.
Juanito, my love.
This should not have happened.
Just wait...
We will see each other again.
Our love...
will be rewritten
on the day of the fourth chance.
Our love...
will be rewritten on the
day of the fourth chance.
1892.
The Revolution's founding year.
It was also the same year
when Dr. Jose Rizal was
captured and exiled to Dapitan.
Blah... blah... blah...
Gosh. I hate this class. So boring.
When will this end?
Before that happened,
Rizal was able to
found La Liga Filipina.
A group who believes
in a quiet and peaceful reform.
However...
After just a few days.
He was arrested.
Read and pass.
And this, so it seems,
And this, so it seems, ignited the
resolve of the young revolutionaries.
That reforms are not enough.
And there must
be actions instead.
What the hell?!
What is happening there?
It's you two again!
If you want to fight,
do it in the Student
Affairs Office.
Alright?!
Not here in my class!
Ew!
How dare you?!
And where are you
going, Ms. Isabella?
Student Affairs Office.
As you advised.
Sir.
It is clearly written in this
college's Code of Conduct
the Rules and
Regulations you violated.
I'm Carmela Isabella.
Soon-to-be twenty. Business
Management student.
Cool, right?
But no. I don't
like any of this.
I just followed my Dad's orders
since he wants
to start a business.
Guess who he wants
to be in charge of it?
Yup. Me. Great.
Miss Isabella, are you with us?
Yes, ma'am.
I really want to quit
if not only for this girl.
'Shae. My childhood
friend turned mortal enemy.
Why?
Because everyone knows her
boyfriend James has a thing for me.
Like I care?!
Since then, it's like she made it
her life's mission to ruin my life.
But I don't want to
give her the satisfaction
to say that I am
a college dropout.
No! Never!
If this happens again, you two
will have a formal disciplinary action.
Girl, you're such a baddie. .
It was bold of you to
walk out of class like that.
But wait... What if
Professor Luis fails you?
Like, duh?
What is even the point of History class
when we're Business Management students?
And besides,
will we ever use those
lessons in modern times?
Carmela,
there's a saying na
"those who doesn't learn
from history are doomed
to repeat it."
Yeah, she's right.
Scary. For real.
You know, if I were you,
I'll just make up during our
group reporting next week.
Don't forget, it's about
the history of San Alfonso.
Hey!
- Don't you have relatives there?
- Yeah.
Next week?
But it's my birthday. Besides,
it's been so long
since I've been there.
Girl, stop.
You will really fail to
graduate if you exit from there.
There.
- Here?
- Uh-huh.
- You believe in superstitions?
- Yeah!
Hey, Carmela.
Our school was established
in the 17th century.
Many before you have
proven it to be true.
But...
if you don't believe it...
Go ahead.
Pass through it.
You know I don't fear anything.
Wow.
Hazel, Angelica!
- The dog's here.
- Hi!
You! Stop right there!
Hey! Carmela!
Why did she run?
Hey...
Carms.
Carmela.
Will you be at my
house party tonight?
Everyone's gonna be there.
Not me.
I didn't know you love
reading history books.
James, what do you care?
What about our past together?
Our history.
I have long moved
on from the past.
And I hate history.
Carmela.
Come here.
So, obviously,
James hasn't been
able to move on from you.
He was just asking if
I'm gonna be at his party.
As if anyone's
gonna be there, right?
Us?!
I know that Shae's just planning
to make me jealous at James' party.
But I don't care.
Hello mic test.
Looks like you're
having too much fun.
Oh!
Why are you looking
at me that way?
Wanna fight?
You want trouble?
If she's not gonna
fight, then I will.
Is that so?
OMG!
How dare you?!
Hey...
Are you okay?
You didn't need to help me.
I can handle it myself.
I just don't like seeing
someone getting bullied.
Besides, why did
you just let her be?
There are other ways to fight.
Also, my Dad is expecting a
lot from me. I can't let him down.
You're just saying that because
you haven't experienced pain yet.
Will you really not
do anything right?!
Problems are the
only thing you give me!
Please, Tita. Not here.
Oh, so now you're embarrassed?
You know shame when
you're reprimanded in public.
But you don't give a damn
when it's me getting shamed
because of your actions!
If I only knew you'll
turn out like this,
I will not have
supported your studies!
Can I?
Of course. Go ahead, try it.
Can i see?
Go on.
So pretty. Who are you again?
By the way...
Are you living here by yourself?
Well...
I have two younger sisters.
But they'll be home later
from school.
And your parents?
My mom passed
away when I was eight.
And my Dad...
He's always busy
with work, so...
...he doesn't really come home.
At least your Dad is just at
work and will eventually be home.
As for me,
both my parents are gone.
That's why my aunt
is taking care of me.
She's the one you're
talking to earlier?
If ever you need someone to
make you smile, I'll be here.
You can drop by here anytime.
I shouldn't have taken you in!
You should've
been better off alone!
Hey, Carmela!
Jenny, Emily. Why
are you still awake?
How about you?
Where have you been?
Dad, I just went to my
friend's birthday party.
Who that might be?
It's Shae.
I thought you and Shae
are no longer friends?
And also,
Mrs. Falcon called me earlier.
She said you and Shae interrupted
your Philippine History class.
Dad...
It was just a petty fight.
Besides, I don't
have time for that.
Actually, I was studying
in the library earlier.
So how do you explain this? Huh?
Why are your grades so low?
im screwed
Did you know you left
your computer open?
Your school portal!
There! I printed it!
Carmela...
why can't you be
like your cousins?
Look at them!
They're already successful!
And you?
You're left behind!
See?
I know that already!
Carmela.
My child...
You know why I'm doing this.
Because I care for you.
Always.
Good night, Dad.
Good night.
And you two,
go to bed now!
- Yes, Dad.
- Okay.
You're getting used to this.
- Go to sleep.
- Yes, Dad.
Good night. Love you.
Good night!
Love you.
Always like this...
It's always like this.
I wish you were here, Ma.
Maybe things will be different.
I miss you.
How much rice do you want?
That's enough.
- More.
- I was first.
Mommy!
Carmela, please.
That is Jenny's seat.
- Come on, child.
- But Mommy...
Come on, child.
Please, Carmela.
You are the eldest.
- Carmela.
- So unfair.
Carmela, it's not unfair.
You are eldest.
You should...
always put your sister first.
Right? What if we're
not around anymore--
Carmenia,
- David, I think...
- What?
I think the baby's coming.
- Mommy!
- I think the baby's coming!
Mommy, Mommy!
Hi Daddy!
- Hi baby!
Jenny, look. We
have a new sister.
- Look! It's our new baby.
- So cute!
She's really cute, isn't she?
Daddy, where's Mommy?
Mommy?
Mommy?!
Mommy, where are you?
Daddy... where's Mommy?
Carmela, Daddy loves
you very much, okay?
It's just that...
Mommy's not gonna come home.
Emily?
Emily!
You rascal! Emily!
Ew. Is that your
new facial mask?
Ew? Do you want some too?
You want it too, huh?!
Hey, hey, hey.
What's happenening?
Stop -- I said stop!
I already asked you to quit it.
Dad...
Are you still mad at me?
Carmela...
I will never be mad at you.
Come here.
You know what?
Daddy's a bit grumpy.
Strict.
But when I tell you off,
it doesn't mean
that I don't love you.
I love you and your
sisters very much.
Okay?
Dad.
Why are there luggages outside?
Are we going somewhere?
We're going to San Alfonso.
Huh?
Your Grandma Carmina
is making a request.
She's asking us to visit
before your birthday.
So, we're spending
the weekend there.
What?!
I'll be stuck in the
province for two days?!
You know it's been awhile
since we last visited her.
I know your Mom
will be happy if we go.
Alright, that's it.
Just get the bag of gifts we'll
be giving your Grandma. Okay?
- Put it in the car.
- Mm-hmm.
I'll be upstairs.
Jenny, you heard what Dad said.
Get the bag of
gifts. Put it in the car.
Why me?
Dad told you to
do it, didn't he?
You know what to do.
Why is it always me in the end?!
Shhh.
I'm older than you, remember?
But Carmela...
Come on, Jenny.
Let's go upstairs.
So unfair!
Carmela.
Is there wi-fi here?
I hope so.
It has been 12 years,
since i last visited this place
I stil remember i held
my 7th birthday here
I've been waiting for
you for a long time. Jenny.
You're all looking
beautiful. Emily.
Grandma.
Carmela...
1...
2...
3...
4...
5!
Seriously?
10 seconds?
Gosh! what has
been with grandma?
- Mom.
- Oh, David.
We brought you something.
Oh, you shouldn't have.
Come on, girls. Get
inside the house.
Alright.
Carmela, why did Grandma
look at you that way?
I dont' know.
- I know why.
- And why's that?
She probably thinks
you're quite ugly.
Wow! Jenny!
These paintings are beautiful.
Cool!
It's like we're in a museum.
Don't you think?
Cool? More like creepy.
These stuff are far
older than any of us.
Ghosts are probably
haunting this place!
So that's why Mom said she insisted
on studying in Manila for college.
Because she feels as if there's
something weird in their house.
- Jenny, look!
- It's beautiful...
Carmela,
look. It's Mommy.
She's so pretty.
It's too bad. You
didn't get to meet her.
Hey...
Don't get upset about it.
At least you got Mom's beauty.
Right, Jenny?
That's right. We
both got Mom's looks.
Ohhhh, is that so?
Then how about Carmela?
Ohhhh...
So that's why Lola's
looking at you all weird.
So, that's how you
wanna play, huh?
Thank you.
That's Lucia and
her twin sister.
They are the daughters
of my friend, Choleng.
They are the ones helping
me around the house.
Go on, you must eat a lot.
- Have a bite. It's delicious.
- Here, have some relleno.
Emily, eat some vegetables.
- Here, vegetables.
- That's right.
Eat your veggies.
The last time you were here...
It was on your 7th birthday.
Do you still remember
that, Carmela?
Yes, Grandma.
Mom, I do apologize.
We haven't been
able to visit you here.
Don't worry about that anymore.
We have always talked
to each other on the phone.
Alright, you should all eat
now before the food gets cold.
What's wrong?
It isn't to your liking?
Mom...
I just remembered Carmenia.
Her caldereta is
exactly like this.
Really, Dad? Mommy's
cooking was like this?
I taught her the recipe.
It was passed down
from my ancestors.
And that is why...
You kids must learn how to cook
...caldereta like a Montecarlos.
So that you can also teach
it to the next generation.
But, Grandma... your
surname's not Montecarlos, right?
But our family came from the
ancestry of the Montecarlos.
That's why we are still Montecarlos.
And that will never change.
No matter how many
generations pass.
So, learn how to cook...
Caldereta.
Especially you.
So dramatic. Am
I really that ugly?
But I'm very pretty!
Why did Grandma
looked at me that way?
But in fairness...
Bet.
I like this room. It's very...
Very classic.
But it's a bit... scary.
Why did Grandma made us
sleep in separate rooms? Gosh...
Carmela?
Oh my gosh!
Our Father who art in Heaven...
Holy be thy name.
Thy kingdom come--
Carmela?
Child!
Grandma...
I thought you were
something else.
Why aren't you sleeping?
It's too early, Grandma.
Actually, I would usually
go home by midnight.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- You're not sleepy yet?
- Not yet.
Okay. Come with me. There's
something I want to show you.
Whoa...
Oh my God, Grandma.
I didn't know there's a
place like this in this mansion.
Oh my God... it's like
the National Library!
Jenny will find this amazing
because she loves to read!
Wow...
Oh my God, Grandma!
This is just like the secret
doors I saw on movies!
Oh my God!
Follow me.
OMG! Is this where
Grandma keeps her wealth?
I can't breathe. Inheritance
is waving! I'll be rich!
OMG! Is this where
Grandma keeps her wealth?
Come inside, Carmela.
Don't be shy. This is your home.
Okay... I'll admit. Grandma's
smile was a bit creepy.
But with all the expensive things in here,
I wonder how much I can sell them for.
Grandma?
Why did you bring me here?
You know, if we also bring
Dad, Jenny, and Emily here...
They'll be excited
to see all of these.
I want you to meet someone.
What?
Meet someone?
So there's no inheritance?
Gosh...
Is Grandma hiding a hermit in
here that she wants me to befriend?
Our love...
will be rewritten on the
day of the fourth chance.
nosebleed!
Nevermind.
It's time to party!
did you know, you almost got in
trouble? because of your foolishness!
Dad, what's this?
You're now a
collector of old stuffs?
Mother!
mother!
Where am I?
What is this place?
what's wrong with all of you?
there's no other way...
for you to go back to your time!
if you don't finish
your mission here.
Miss Carmelita!
You should not end up together!
You have to keep yourself from
falling for him and him to you!